<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Le Nhan Pham</title>
    <link>https://lenhanpham.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Le Nhan Pham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:52:06 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lenhanpham.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Force fields for water–surface interaction: is reproduction of the experimental water contact angle enough?</title>
      <link>https://lenhanpham.github.io/post/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:52:06 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lenhanpham.github.io/post/homepage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new protocol based on quantum chemical calculations and molecular dynamics simulations is proposed to revisit water–MoS2 interfacial force fields (FFs). The accurate reproduction of experimental water contact angles is suggested to be insufficient to ensure reliable FFs for recovering structural properties of the interfacial solvent. As an example, this protocol is used to develop a new set of FF parameters to both capture interfacial structural phenomena at the interface between water and MoS2 and recover experimental water contact angle data. This approach can be applied to any interface where contact angle data are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Our recently accepted paper in &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ChemCommun?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;@ChemCommun&lt;/a&gt; proposes a novel criterion and then a new protocol for assessment and development of interfacial force fields. Very excited to share it here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/9OD4VZeXQO&#34;&gt;https://t.co/9OD4VZeXQO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Le Nhan Pham (@LeNhanPham1) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LeNhanPham1/status/1366194038232150020?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;March 1, 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://lenhanpham.github.io/vietnamese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 22:59:09 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lenhanpham.github.io/vietnamese/</guid>
      <description>Thông tin chung Phạm Lê Nhân tốt nghiệp tiến sỹ tại Khoa hóa học, Đại học Leuven (tháng 9, năm 2019).
Chuyên ngành nghiên cứu: Hóa lý thuyết và tính toán.
Email: Lenhanhoaqn[@]gmail.com
Lý lịch khoa học: Le-Nhan-Pham.pdf
Giới thiệu hướng nghiên cứu Các hướng nghiên cứu của Phạm Lê Nhân tập trung vào một số lĩnh vực chuyên sâu. Nhìn chung, hiện nay tác giả đang đi vào hai hướng chính liên quan đến nghiên cứu cơ bản vật liệu vô cơ dạng cụm nguyên tử (clusters) và vật liệu ứng dụng trong trong công nghệ sinh học.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lenhanpham.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 20:01:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lenhanpham.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;le-nhan-pham&#34;&gt;LE NHAN PHAM&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/1215084408325099522/WtlTgsec_400x400.jpg&#34; width=&#34;170&#34;/&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a chemist whose research experience is related to physical &amp;amp; theoretical chemistry and materials, particularly atomic clusters, excited states,  and currently 2D&amp;amp;biological materials. I graduated (Ph.D.) from  Department of Chemistry, University of Leuven, Belgium (September 2019), and is currently working as a postdoctoral research fellow at Deakin  University and visiting scholar at Department of Physics, RMIT,  Australia. I was also a yearly-contract lecturer at Department of  Chemistry, University of Dalat, Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lenhanpham.github.io/vietnamese/&#34; title=&#34;Click để xem bằng Tiếng Việt&#34;&gt;Giới thiệu về nghiên cứu của Phạm Lê Nhân bằng Tiếng Việt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://lenhanpham.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 19:59:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lenhanpham.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>Publications  Pham, L. N.; Walsh, T. R. Force Fields for Water–Surface Interaction: Is Reproduction of the Experimental Water Contact Angle Enough? Chem. Commun. 2021, 57 (27), 3355–3358. doi:10.1039/d1cc00426c. Pham, L. N.; Russo, S. P. Energetic Degeneracy and Electronic Structures of Germanium Trimers Doped with Titanium. J. Chem. Phys. 2020, 153 (7), 074309. doi:10.1063/5.0016230. Pham, L. N.; van Dijk, C. N.; Kirilyuk, A.; Goerigk, L.; Nguyen, M. T.; Janssens, E. Structures and Magnetism of Cationic Chromium&amp;ndash;Manganese Bimetallic Oxide Clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://lenhanpham.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lenhanpham.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research  2D nanomaterials and biological materials Molecular dynamics force field development Semiconductor clusters doped with transition metals Transition metal oxide magnetic materials  Programing 1. A simple Hartree-Fock program written in Python 3 In an attempt to learn programming, I have created a small program written in Python 3, which can solve the Schrodinger equation for HHe+ at the Hartree-Fock level. If you are interested in Python programming and basic quantum chemical theory, just have a look at it (on Github).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
